Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - T
    - Taggart, Herbert F., Accounting; Business Administration, 1966, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Tai, Chen To, Electrical Engineering, 1964, 1979, 1987, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Takahei, Tetsuo, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Institute of Science and Technology, 1961, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Takeashita, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Talayco, John, French, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Tamres, Milton, Chemistry, 1960, 1966, 1973 (Box 13)
      (na 2151 - 2)
    - Tannenbaum, Arnold S., Survey Research Center, 1955, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Tanner, Helen H., Center for Continuing Education for Women, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Tanner, Wilson P. Jr., Research Institute, Electronic Defense Group, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Tanter, Raymond, Political Science, 1978, 1973, 1981, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Tapia, James, Marching Band, 1999, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Tarbox, Joseph G., Electrical Engineering, 1958, 1959 (Box 13)
      (na 2655)
    - Tashian, Richard E., Human Genetics, Medical School, 1961 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, James R., School of Business Administration, 1968, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Joseph, Engineering, 1960, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Margaret, Information and Library Studies, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Martha, ITD, 1998 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Mary, Sociology, 1951 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Philip, Political Science (Box 13)
      (na 2750)
    - Taylor, Robert, School of Social Work, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Robert C., Chemistry, 1958 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Simone Himbeault, Career Planning and Placement, 1996, 1993, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Thomas, Music, 1976, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, William Randolph, Botany, 1961 (Box 13)
    - Teal, Laurence L., Music, 1972, 1978, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Tedesco, Lisa, VP and Secretary, 1999 (Box 13)
    - Teig, Janice, Information and News Service, 1960 (Box 13)
      (nb 781 - 2)
    - Tejada, Irene, University School, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Tek, M. Rasin, Chemical Engineering, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Telfer, Jack, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Telfer, William (Box 13)
    - Ten Have, Ralph, Maternal and Child Health, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Tennent, Doris, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Teorey, Toby, C.I.T.I., 1992 (Box 13)
    - Terpestra, Vern, Business Admin., 1966, 1978, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Teske, Richard, Astronomy, 1984, 1980, 1965, 1977, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Test, Fred, Zoology, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Thelander, Albert, Air Science, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Therkelsen, E. B. (Box 13)
    - Thiel, Donald, Staff Benefits, Office of, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Thiele, Dennis, Biological Chemistry, Medical School, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Thieme, Frederick, Anthropology, 1957 (Box 13)
      (na 2748)
    - Thigpen, Jacquline, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Thiry, James R., Personnel, 1984, 1966, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Thoburn, Norman L., Diabetes Research and Training, 1982, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Arthur L., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Deaver, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Edwin J., School of Social Work, 1958, 1968, 1965, 1986, 1978, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Jacob, Accounting, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Marlin U., Indus. And Op. Eng., 1978 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Morgan, Political Science, 1952 (Box 13)
      (na 2747)
    - Thomas, Norman C., Political Science, LS&A, 1963, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Pat, Housing, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Thomas, Patricia, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Thomassen, Lars, Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Thomet, Glen A., Alumni Association, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Clyde H., Music, 1956, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Douglas F., Engineering Graphics, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Gerald, School of Business Administration, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Ian M., Medical School, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Levi, Chemical Engineering, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Thompson, Sue, Affirmative Action, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Thorby, Jean, Medical Care, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Thorpe, Gordon L., Naval Science, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Thorton, Jesse, English (Box 13)
      (na 2745)
    - Thrall, Robert M., Mathematics, Engineering, 1960, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Thrupp, Sylvia L., History, 1961, 1962, 1965 (Box 13)
      (nb 789 - 92)
    - Thuma, Burton D., Psychology, Associate Dean of LS&A, 1963 (Box 13)
      (na 2151 - 65)
    - Thurber, Donald M. D., Regent, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Tiboni, Emil A., School of Public Health, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Tice, Terrence, Education, 1971, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Tiedeman, Walter D., Environmental Health, 1959 (Box 13)
      (na 2744)
    - Tien, T. Y., Chemical Engineering; Materials Engineering, 1966, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Tietze, Christopher, Population Council (Box 13)
    - Tikofsky, Ronald, Speech, Speech Clinic, 1962, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Tilley, Morris P. (Box 13)
    - Tilly, Charles, Sociology/History, 1974, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Tilly, Louise A., History, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Tirrell, John E., Alumni Association, 1958, 1962 (Box 13)
      (na 2166)
    - Titiev, Mischa, Anthropology (Box 13)
      (na 2167)
    - Titus, Gordon, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Tobler, Waldo, Geography, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Tocher, Stewert R., Natural Resources, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Todd, William L., 1952 (Box 13)
      (na 2743)
    - Todor, John, 1975, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Toliver, Z. Edmon, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Toller, John, Human Resources, 1998, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Toneye, Rod, Affirmative Action (Box 13)
    - Tonge, Gina, Parent Orientation Program (Box 13)
    - Tons, Egons, Civil Engineering, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Tonsor, Stephen, Math, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Tonsor, Stephen J., History, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Topping, Roberta, Affirmative Action, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Torchinsky, Abe, Music, 1979, 1974, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Tordoff, Harrison B., Zoology Department, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Torrez, Edward, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Toussaint, Maynard N., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 13)
      (nb 793 - 95)
    - Townley, Charles, Library Science, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Townsend, Richard E., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Towsley, Harry, Medical School, 1956 (Box 13)
    - Tracy, John E., Law (Box 13)
    - Trapp, Marilynn, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Traugott, Michael, Communication Studies; Institute for Social Research, 1999, 1992, 1988, 1980, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Trautmann, Thoams, History, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Travers, Lee Sumter, Economics, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Tribus, Myron, Engineering, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Trilling, George H., Physics, 1959 (Box 13)
      (nb 1165, nb1176)
    - Trinkhaus, Charles, History, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Trojan, Paul K., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Tropman, John, School of Social Work, 1984, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Troth, Eugene, Music, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Trotter, Eugene, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Trow, Elizabeth (Box 13)
    - Trow, William Clark, Education, Psychology, 1959 (Box 13)
      (nb 1014, nb 1015, nb 1016)
    - Trowbridge, Leslie W., Education, University School, 1961 (Box 13)
    - True, Nelita, Music, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Truzzi, Marcello, Social Work?, 1969, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Trytten, John M, Education, 1957, 1960, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Tsao, Makepeace U., Biochemistry, Medical School, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Tubbs, Linford, Food Service, 1981, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Tuel, William S., Staff Systems Planning, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Tuer, Jill, ITD, 1988, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Tulliver, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Tupper, Charles J., Internal Medicine, Medical School, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Turcotte, Jeremiah G., Surgery, 1963, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Turneaure, Frederick S., Geology, 1961 (Box 13)
    - Turner, Robert L., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 13)
      (nb 1263)
    - Turner, William H., Social Work, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Twiddle, Beth, 1957 (Box 13)
      (na 2737, na 2738, na 2739, na 2740, na 2741)
    - Tyler, Monica, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Tyler, Veronica, Voice (Box 13)
  - U
    - Uberoi, Mahinder S., Aeronautical Engineering, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Ueker, Alfred B., Personnel, 1957 (Box 14)
    - Uhlenbeck, George E., Physics, 1953 (Box 14)
      (na 2736)
    - Uhlendorf, Bernhard A., UMRI (Box 14)
    - Ulllman, Betty M., Conductron, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Ullman, Joseph L., Math, 1959, 1978, 1966, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Ulrich, Dean Beverly, Kinesiology, 2001, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Umstadter, Donald, Engineering, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Upatnieks, Juris, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1978, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Upham, Mrs., 1958 (Box 14)
      (nb 1012, nb 1013)
    - Upshur, John A., English Language Institute, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Upthegrove, Clair, 1953 (Box 14)
      (na 2735)
    - Urist, Rachelle, Drama, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Uttal, William, Pyschology and, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Uzoigwe, Godfrey N., History, 1978, 1971 (Box 14)
  - V
    - Vainstein, Rose, Library Science, 1974, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Valusek, John E., Education, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Van Aken, Elbert W., Bureau of Appointments and Occupational Information, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Van Demark, Ann, Speech and Hearing Sciences, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Van den Bosch, Gsovert W., ISR, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Van Der Merwe, Johan, Opera, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Van der Schalie, Henry, Zoology, 1952, 1975, 1964 (Box 14)
      (na 2182)
    - Van der Voo, Rob, Geology, 1973, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Van Der Walker, Edward J., Campus Mail (Box 14)
      (na 2732-2733)
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1951 (Box 14)
      (na 2731)
    - Van Duren, Arthur, LS&A (Box 14)
      (na 2730)
    - Van Houweling, Douglas E., Information Technology, 1986, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Van Leer, Bram, Aerospace Engineering, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Van Messel, James, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Van Steenburgh, Elston W., Appointed to faculty of UM Flint Senior College (Box 14)
    - Van Syoc, Bryce, English, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Van Tyne, Josselyn, Zoology, 1953 (Box 14)
    - Van Vlack, Lawrence H., Materials and Metallurgical Engineering, 1959, 1983, 1968, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Van Voorhees, Curtis, Education, 1971, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Van Wylen, Gordon J., Mechanical Engineering, 1955, 1960, 1967, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Vance, Kenneth, Bureau of School Services; Library Science, 1954, 1969, 1971 (Box 14)
    - VandenBosch, Elizabeth, Alumni Association, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Vander Velde, John C., Physics, 1961, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Vander Weg, John, Music, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Vander, Arthur, Physiology, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Vanderhoff, Herbert, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 14)
    - VanderVelde, Edward, Geography, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Vanderwill, Wayne, Personnel, 1971 (Box 14)
    - VanMater, Paul R., Jr., Naval Architecture, 1963 (Box 14)
    - VanSelow, Neal, 1967 (Box 14)
    - Van't Hul, Bernard, English Language and Literatures & Res., 1974 (Box 14)
    - VanVliet, Alyce, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 14)
    - VanZyle, Gerrit, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Varner, Nellie M., Political Science, 1977, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Vaughan, Henry F., School of Public Health (Box 14)
    - Vaughan, Rebecca, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Vaux, Henry, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Veltman, Martinus J. G., Physics, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Velz, Clarence, Public Health Engineering, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Vergon, Charles, SEB, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Vernon, Manfred C., Political Science (Box 14)
      (na 2724, na 2725, na 2726, na 2727)
    - Veroff, Joseph, Survey Research Center (Box 14)
    - Veronda, Carlo, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Vesper, F. J., Mechanical Engineering (Box 14)
    - Vest, Charles M., Mechanical Engineering, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Vetter, Eric W., School of Business Administration, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Vezzani, Almondo A., Vocational Education and Practical Arts, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Vial, A. Burgess, Surgery, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Vibrans, Frank, Naval Architecture, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Vidar, Frede, Drawing and Painting, College of Architecture and Design, 1963 (Box 14)
      (na 2201-03)
    - Villarreal, Julian E., Pharmacology, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Villars, Trudy (Box 14)
    - Vincent, Dietrich H., Nuclear Engineering, 1961, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Vincent, Donald E., Library Services, Dearborn Center, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Vincent, Edward T., Mechanical Engineering, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Vines, Quentin C., Industrial Engineering, 1954 (Box 14)
    - Vinh, Nguyen Xuan, Aerospace Engineering, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Vining, Joseph, Law, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Vinovskis, Maris, History, 1979, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Vinter, Robert D., School of Social Work, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Vivian, Weston E., Research Institute, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Vogler, Daniel E., Education, 1971, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Vogt, Suzanne, Michigan Alumnus, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Vokac, Robert, 1968 (Box 14)
      (na 2766)
    - Volakis, John, EECS, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Vollmer, Joseph H., SEB, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Volz, Richard, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Volz, Richard A., Electrical Engineering, 1971, 1978, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Voorhees, John J., Dermatology (Box 14)
    - Vorus, William S., NAME, College of Engineering (Box 14)
    - Voss, Burton, Education, 1975, 1991, 1967, 1971, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Voss, Edward G., Herbarium, 1956, 1968, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Vosu, Ted, College of Engineering, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Vredevoe, Lawrence, UCLA, 1971 (Box 14)
      (na 2723)
    - Vroman, Clyde, Admissions; Music, 1958, 1957, 1960, 1962 (Box 14)
  - V
    - Vroom, Victor, Survey Research Center, 1958 (Box 14)
  - W
    - Wade, Barbara, Physical Education, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Wagman, Frederick H., University Library, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Wagner, Brent, School of Music, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Wagner, Herbert P., Food Service, 1959, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Wagner, Leslie E., Mechanical Engineering, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Wagner, Warren H., Jr., Botany, 1964, 1975, 1978, 1980, 1986, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Wahr, Fred B., German, 1948 (Box 14)
      (na 2208-10, na 5689)
    - Waite, John B., Law, 1951 (Box 14)
    - Wakefield, Floyd, Property Control, Willow Run Airport, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Walcott, Fred, Education, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Wald, Alan, English and American Culture, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Walker, Charles, Zoology, 1959, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Walker, Edward L., Psychology, 1962, 1963, 1970, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Walker, Jack L., Public Administration; Policy Science and Public Policy, 1968, 1980, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Walker, James C. G., Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, 1984, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Wall, Jim, Athletics, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Wallace, Charles, Data Systems Center, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Wallace, Herschel, Student Services, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wallace, James B., Music Literature, 1960, 1965, 1977 (Box 14)
      (na 2214)
    - Wallace, Michael, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Wallace, Victor L., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Wallach, William K., Bentley Historical Library, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Wallendorf, Melanie R., Marketing, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Waller, Bret, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Waller, Patricia, UMTRI, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Walser, Rob, School of Music, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Walsh, Patricia, Public Health Nursing, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Walter, C. J. (Box 14)
    - Walter, Tim, Reading, Learning Skills Center; Reading Improvement Services, 1989, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Walter, Timothy, Sports Management, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Walters, John, WUOM, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Walton, Kendall L., Philosophy, 1979, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Waltz, Frederick M., Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Walz, Garry, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Wang, Henry, Chemical Engineering, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wang, Lumin, Engineering, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Wang, Thomas, School of Natural Resources (Box 14)
    - Wang, William S., Speech, 1960 (Box 14)
      (nb 1009, 1010, 1011)
    - Wangler, John, Athletic Dept., 1982 (Box 14)
    - Wanstrom, Ruth C., Pathology, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Ward, Robert E., Political Science, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Wardel, Donald C., Real Estate, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Warden, Eric, Education, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Wardhaugh, Ronald, English Language Institute, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Warner, David E., 1971 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Jack D., Speech and Hearing Sciences, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Kate, Urban Planning, 1975, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Kenneth, Health Planning and Administration, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Paul E., 1968 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Robert A., Music, 1973, 1960, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Robert M., Bentley Historical Library, 1961, 1980, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Robert M., Bentley Historical Library, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Warner, Sam B., History, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Austin, English, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Donald W., Mathematics, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Larry, University of Michigan Hospitals, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Warshaw, Martin R., Marketing, 1960, 1966, 1971, 1975, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Washington, Monique, Undergraduate Admissions, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Washington, Von, Black Theater Workshop, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Washington, Warren, Engineering, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Wasson, Harry, Systems and Data Processing, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Waterman, Margeret, Alumni Activities, 1956 (Box 14)
      (na 2713)
    - Waterman, Merwin, Finance, 1950, 1966, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Waters, James, Regent, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Waterson, Jane, Law School, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Watkin, Kenneth, Education (Box 14)
    - Watkins, Ed, University Press, 1957 (Box 14)
    - Watkins, Glen, Musicology, School of Music, 1972, 1976, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Watkins, Herbert, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Watkins, Kenneth L., Speech and Hearing Sciences, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Watlington, Malchus, Div. Management Education, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Watson, Andrew, Psychiatry (Medical and Law School), 1959, 1967, 1974, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Watson, David W., 1967 (Box 14)
    - Watson, Joseph, Building Serv., Plant, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Weaver, Bennett, English, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Weaver, Donald C., Education, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Weaver, Richard, Conservation, School of Natural Resources, 1957 (Box 14)
    - Webb, James, Chemistry?, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Webb, Paul W., Fisheries, School of Natural Resources, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Webb, Philip E., Engineering, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Weber, Albert J., Design, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Weber, Walter J., Jr., Civil Engineering, 1987, 1964, 1963, 1985, 1973, 1978 (Box 14)
      (nb 987-990)
    - Weber, Wendell W., Pharmacology, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Weddige, Emil, Design, 1957, 1954 (Box 14)
      (na 2216)
    - Weeks, H. Ashley, Bureau of Public Health Economics, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Weeks, Robert P., English, 1977, 1975, 1961 (Box 14)
      (na 2217-20)
    - Wegman, Myron E., Public Health, 1971, 1965, 1979, 1982, 1981, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wehmeyer, Lewis E., Botany, 1955 (Box 14)
    - Wehrer, Joseph J., Architecture, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Weichlein, William J., Music Literature, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Weick, Karl E., School of Business Administration, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Weidenbach, Jack, 1989, 1983, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Weikart, Phyllis, Physical Education & Athletics, 1975, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Weil, Mrs., 1968 (Box 14)
    - Weil, Herschel, Electrical Engineering, 1960, 1964, 1978, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Weimer, Patricia M., Reading Clinic, Children's Psychiatric Hospital (Box 14)
      (na 2716)
    - Weinberg, Gerhard L., History, 1960, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Weinberg, Louis, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Weiner, Norm, Pharm., 1973 (Box 14)
    - Weinreich, Gabriel, Physics, 8/3/1967, 1983, 8/1975 (Box 14)
    - Weinstein, David, Pediatrics, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Weinstein, Stephen B., Electrical Engineering, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Weintraub, Daniel, Psych., 1967 (Box 14)
    - Weir, John, English Language Institute, 1954, 1967 (Box 14)
      (na 2221-24)
    - Weisfeld, Zelma H., Speech Communication and Theatre, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Weiss, Benjamin, Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Weiss, Carol, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Weiss, Edward (Box 14)
    - Weiss, Kathleen, Business School, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Weiss, Robert, Institute for Social Research, 1955 (Box 14)
    - Welch, Harold J., Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Welch, Paul, Zoology, 1951 (Box 14)
    - Weldon, William S., 1959, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Weller, Thomas, 1956 (Box 14)
      (na 2717)
    - Welliver, Harry, Broadcasting Service, Radio WUOM, 1964, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Wellman, Henry M., Psychology, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Wellman, John D., ISR, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Wellman, Richard D., Law, 1960, 1968, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Wells, Carlton, English; Education, 1964, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Wells, Robert, Political Science, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Wells, Stanfield M., Michigan Union; VP Community Resource Development, 1970, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wells, Thelma, Nursing, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Wendel, James G., Mathematics, 1960, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Wenrich, Ralph C., Vocational Education and Practical Arts, 1957, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Wentworth, Frederick H., Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Wentzel, Donat G., Anatomy, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Wenzel, Richard L., Public Health Administration, 1963, 1962, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Werner, William, Architecture, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Wernette, J. Philip, Business Administration, 1957, 1960, 1954, 1960 (Box 14)
    - West, George L. Jr., Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering; Nuclear Engineering, 1959, 1966 (Box 14)
      (nb 994-999)
    - West, S. Stuart, Survey Research Center, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Westerberg, Martha R., Neurology, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Westerman, W. Scott, Education, 1955 (Box 14)
    - Westervelt, Frank H., Mechanical Engineering, 1954, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Westley, Bruce, 1953 (Box 14)
      (na 2718)
    - Westman, Jack C., Psychiatry, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Weston, Jerome, Financial Analysis, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Weston, Peter K., Law, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wethey, Harold, History of Art, 1964 (Box 14)
      (nb 834-836)
    - Wetzler, Theodore, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, Benjamin W., History, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, James E., Accounting, 1981, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Wheeler, Ray, Music?, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Whelan, Janice, Alumnus, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Wheller, Albert, President of local NAACP, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Whipple, G. Hoyt, Jr., Radiological Health, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Whitaker, Gilbert R., Jr., Business, 1992, 1988, 1978, 1987 (Box 14)
    - White, B. Joseph, Business Administration, 1994, 1988, 1975, 1980 (Box 14)
    - White, David, Natural Resources, 1979 (Box 14)
    - White, Gilbert, Cook Lecturer, 1966 (Box 14)
    - White, James J., Law, 1970 (Box 14)
    - White, Jim, 1964 (Box 14)
      (nb 1000-1002)
    - White, John P., Political Science, 1962 (Box 14)
    - White, Kenneth S., French, 1962 (Box 14)
    - White, Leslie A., Anthropology, 1958, 1969 (Box 14)
    - White, Robert R., Chemical Engineering, 1949 (Box 14)
      (na 2719)
    - White, Timothy, Kinesiology, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Whitehead, Lawrence, Environmental and Industrial Health, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Whitesell, Joseph, Mechanical Engineering, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Whiteside, Kathy, Housing, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Whitfield, Carolyn D., Biological Chemistry, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Whitfield, Harvey J., Biological Chemistry, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Whiting, Allen S., Political Science, 1975, 1971, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Whitman, Christina, Law (Box 14)
    - Whitman, Mrs. C. (Box 14)
    - Whitman, Nathan, History of Art, 1965 (Box 14)
    - Whitmire, Anthony, Music, 1952 (Box 14)
      (na 2720)
    - Whitsett, Ora, Housing, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Whittaker, Pru, Development, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Whittes, Simon, Education, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Wieck, Fred, University Press, 1954 (Box 14)
      (na 2721)
    - Wiegand, Nancy, English, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Wielanga, Geert, Education, 1958 (Box 14)
    - Wier, John, English Language Institute, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Wight, James K., Civil Engineering, 1978, 1993, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Wiin-Nielsen, Aksel, Meteorology, 1963, 1973, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Wikelund, Philip R., 1950 (Box 14)
    - Wild, Edmund, German (Box 15)
      (na 5688)